=A Love Journal= =Episode 21=
= مجلة الحب = = الحلقة 21 =
♪You have a dazzling smile♪
♪ لديك ابتسامة مبهرة ♪
♪Like sunshine♪
♪ كالشمس المشرقة ♪
♪Every day is new with you♪
♪ كل يوم جديد معك
♪By my side♪
♪ بجانبي ♪
♪Handsome and cute, you win my heart♪
♪ وسيم ولطيف تكسب قلبي
♪Energy and good luck forever♪
الطاقة ونتمنى لك التوفيق إلى الأبد ♪
I am hungry.
أنا جائع.
♪All growth contains wind and rain♪
كل النمو يحتوي على الرياح والأمطار ♪
Me too.
أنا أيضاً.
♪Little by little, your love gathers to the end of the earth♪
شيئًا فشيئًا ، حبك يتجمع إلى آخر الأرض
I'm really hungry.
أنا حقا جائع.
♪The world is big but you're by my side♪
♪ العالم كبير لكنك بجانبي
I'm really hungry too.
أنا جائع حقًا.
♪Energy and good luck forever♪
الطاقة ونتمنى لك التوفيق إلى الأبد ♪
Gu Shen, don't...
قو شين ، لا ...
♪Good luck♪
♪ حظ سعيد ♪
♪I heard people who always smile have good luck♪
♪ سمعت أن الناس الذين يبتسمون دائمًا يحالفهم الحظ
♪You prove with facts that it is true♪
تثبت بالحقائق أنه صحيح
♪All the good things are around you♪
كل الأشياء الجيدة من حولك
♪You're the luckiest one♪
♪ أنت الأكثر حظًا
♪So I'm at ease♪
♪ إذن أنا مرتاح ♪
♪Hold your hand and go♪
♪ امسك يدك وانطلق ♪
♪Be optimistic and don't be afraid♪
♪ كن متفائلاً ولا تخاف ♪
♪With you along the way♪
معك على طول الطريق ♪
♪Start a new journey with our original intention♪
♪ ابدأ رحلة جديدة بقصدنا الأصلي ♪
Look at yourself.
انظر الى نفسك.
Mr. Gu has worn Mrs. Gu out.
السيد قو قد أجهد السيدة جو.
You've got
عندك
a dirty mind.
عقل قذر.
Young people.
الشباب.
Restrain yourselves.
كبح جماح أنفسكم.
You.
أنت.
Let me fix you.
دعني اصلحك.
Always talking nonsense.
الحديث دائما هراء.
Enough, enough.
يكفي يكفي.
Be serious.
كن جادا.
We need to maintain the relationship
نحن بحاجة للحفاظ على العلاقة
with the clients of Mrs. Huang.
مع عملاء السيدة هوانغ.
I've made appointments with Hutai and Yinrun.
لقد حددت مواعيد مع Hutai و Yinrun.
Okay.
تمام.
No problem.
لا مشكلة.
I'll meet the people of Yinrun.
سألتقي بأهالي ينرون.
But,
ولكن،
Mr. Lin
السيد لين
has a bad reputation.
له سمعة سيئة.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
I've dealt with such people before.
لقد تعاملت مع هؤلاء الناس من قبل.
I can do it.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك.
Be careful.
كن حذرا.
I think
أظن
you're more dangerous.
أنت أكثر خطورة.
You're young and promising, Mrs. Ning.
أنت شابة وواعدة يا سيدة نينغ.
You're flattering me, Mr. Lin.
أنت تجاملني يا سيد لين.
We must rely on you.
يجب أن نعتمد عليك.
I'm so happy to have such a beautiful girl like you
أنا سعيد جدًا لوجود مثل هذه الفتاة الجميلة مثلك
having dinner with me.
تناول العشاء معي.
We will try our best to give you
سنبذل قصارى جهدنا لنقدم لك
what Mrs. Huang promised you before.
ما وعدتك به السيدة هوانغ من قبل.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Anything I want?
أي شيء أريد؟
Yes.
نعم.
As long as it is reasonable.
طالما كان ذلك معقولاً.
I think
أظن
they are all reasonable.
كلهم معقولون.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.